SHARAREH KESHAVARZI

Toronto, ON M2J 3B9 +1647-447-3080 Keshavarzisharareh@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Experienced and motivated software engineer with 5+ years of experience in delivering high-quality software solutions. Strong team player with in-depth knowledge of development tools and languages. Ambitious and capable of working under pressure, with excellent time management, multi-tasking, and problem-solving skills. Quick learner with an open mind.

EDUCATION

Master of Software Engineering (GPA 3.8)

2019-2021

Concordia University - Montreal, Canada

Courses: Big data analytics ,Software design methodologies, Software Project Management Member of Golden Key International Honor Society

granted membership based on being at the top 15% of the university program

BSc: Information Technology Engineering

2011-2015

Shiraz University of Technology - Shiraz, Iran

Courses : Algorithms and data structure , Operating system , Networks , Database Management System

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

01/2020 - Current

Dolembreux Solutions Réseau - QC, Canada

- Learned and adapted quickly to new technology and software applications.
- Designed, implemented, tested, maintained, refactored code, and updated documentation.
- Skilled in developing software solutions across multiple platforms including Windows, mobile, and web-based applications, with expertise in both front-end and back-end development.

06/2022 - 06/2022 Volunteer

Collision Conference - Toronto, Canada (North America's fastest-growing tech conference)

- Supported engaging and smooth-running events by helping with organization and planning.
- Used strong interpersonal communication skills to convey information to others.

Programmer 06/2016 - 07/2018

Amel System Company - Shiraz, Iran

- Utilized Visual Basic to maintain and enhance a financial software system by implementing new features and ensuring its continued functionality.
- Enhanced software performance by optimizing SQL queries with Microsoft SQL Server , resulting in significantly improved query speed.
- Created and updated comprehensive reports and documentation with attention to detail.

SKILLS

- Java
- C#
- Visual Basic
- Python
- Kotlin
- HTML5
- CSS3
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Node.is
- React.js
- PostgreSQL
- Microsoft SQL Server
- Spark
- Git
- Jira